devguru.com 2019-06-12

# Privacy Statement | DevGuru

Last updated on: 12 June 2018

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to describe how **DevGuru** (located at http://www.devguru.com) collects and uses the information about you. Please read this notice very carefully to understand what we do. 

## Your Privacy

**DevGuru** protects your privacy by following all the legal requirements. 

Our Privacy Policy is a legal statement which explains how we collect and share your information, and how you can limit our sharing of your information. Our security settings protect the misuse of your sensitive information. There will be terms that are capitalized in this Privacy Policy. The meaning of these terms are described below in the Definitions section. 

## Definitions

“Non Personal Information” means information that is personally not identifiable to you and the information that we automatically collect when you access our Website from a browser. It may include publicly available information that is shared between you and the others. 

“Personally Identifiable Information” is non-public information that is personally identifiable to you and obtained from you within our Website. Personally Identifiable Information may include information such as your name, email address, and other related information that you provide to us or that we obtain about you. 

## Information We Collect

Generally, you control the amount and type of information you provide to us when using our Website. 

As a Visitor, you can browse our website to find out more about the website. You won't need to provide us with any of your Personally Identifiable Information as a Visitor. **DevGuru** requires no user registration. All the users are free to visit **DevGuru** without any restrictions. 

## Automatically Collected Information

We automatically collect certain types of usage information when you visit our website. Such information is typically considered as Non Personal Information. This information includes the name of the website from which you entered our Website and also the name of the website to which you are headed next when you leave from our website (if any). This information also includes the IP address of your computer/proxy server that you use to access the Internet, your Internet Website provider name, web browser type, type of mobile device, and computer operating system. 

When you visit our Website, we may send one or more cookies — a text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters — to your computer which helps to uniquely identifies your browser and lets us help you log in faster and enhance your navigation experience throughout the site. A cookie may also convey information to us about how you use the Service (The pages you view, the links you click and other actions you take on the Service), and allow us to track your usage of the Service over time. 

Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of Cookies. However, if you disable the Cookies, you may not be able to access the functionality on our Website properly or nothing at all. We will never place Personal Information in these Cookies.

Cookies are also widely used for online advertising. DevGuru and/or its advertising affiliates shall employ cookies and related technologies to store information on or read information from your browser or device. Some data collected by DevGuru and/or its adverting affiliates may be used for personalized advertising. 

**Note :** Opting out of advertising cookies will not disable ads, they will just no longer be tailored to you. 

  * Google 

  * Vibrant 

If your browser accept cookies, we take this and also your continued use of the website to mean that you are in good terms with this. If you wish to deactivate cookies, you can do this. However doing so will likely mean that your browser will not work as you would expect on most web pages. 

We use all of this information to analyze trends among our Users to help improve our Website. 

## How We Use Your Information

  1. We may share your personal information with: 
    1. Other companies owned by or under common ownership which includes any of our subsidiaries (i.e., any organization we own or control). These companies will use your personal information in the same way as we do as mentioned in this Policy. 

    2. Third party vendors, consultants, contractors and other service providers that perform on our behalf, in order to carry out their work for us, may include content or service fulfillment, accounting, or providing analytics services. We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties for marketing purposes. 

  2. Any information or content that you voluntarily provide us for posting to the Service, such as User Content, becomes available to the public and/or to other members, as controlled by the privacy settings. 
  3. We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties for marketing purposes. We may provide your Personally Identifiable Information to affiliates that provide services to us with regards to our Website. Such affiliates will only receive information necessary to provide the respective services and will be bound by confidentiality agreements limiting the use of such information. 
  4. We retain the right to collect and use any Non Personal Information collected from your use of our Website and aggregate such data for internal analytics that improve our Website and Service as well as for use or resale to others. At no time is your Personally Identifiable Information included in such data cluster. 
  5. We may be legally required to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information, if any such disclosure is - 
    1. Required by subpoena, law, or by other legal process; 

    2. Necessary to assist law enforcement officials or government enforcement agencies; 

    3. Necessary to investigate the violations of or otherwise enforce our Legal Terms; 

    4. Necessary to protect us from the legal action or claims from the third parties including you and/or other Members; and/or 

    5. Necessary to protect the legal rights, personal/real property, or personal safety of **DevGuru** , our Users, employees, and affiliates. 

## Privacy Policy Updates

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy any time we want. You should review this Privacy Policy frequently. If we make any material changes to this policy, we may notify you on our Website, by a blog post, by email, or by any of the method we determine. The method we chose is at our sole discretion. We will also change the “Last Updated” date at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy are effective as of this Last Updated date and replace any prior Privacy Policies. 

## Questions About Our Privacy Practices or This Privacy Policy

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policies or other Practices, you may please contact us.
